<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Monedero electronico Iber</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="qr_code">qr_code</string>
    <string name="enter_your_info">Enter your info</string>
    <string name="generate_qr_code">Generate QR Code</string>
    <string name="toggle_flash">Toggle Flash</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="scanned_data">Scanned Data</string>
    <string name="politica">"This privacy policy is used to inform you regarding policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use this Service.\n
1. Overview \n
  Camera \n
Among the functions of our app; It is establishing payments using QR codes, to perform the qr code scan access to the device camera is necessary, we only use the camera permission for that purpose.
\n

2.0 Google Play Services \n
Google Play Services offers APIs and security services to the Android developer ecosystem.
Google acts as a data controller for any personal data processed in Google Play Services,
and offers user notices and consents about the use of personal data in the service’s user
interface in Android.
Collected informations:
* Device information
* Log information
* Location information
* Unique application numbers
* Local storage
* Cookies and similar technologies \n
Google use the collected information to provide, maintain, protect and improve Google’s
services, to develop new ones, and to protect Google and the users. Google also use this
information to offer you tailored content – like giving you more relevant search results
and ads. \n
Online resources:
* Google Terms of Service https://policies.google.com/terms
* Google Privacy Policy https://policies.google.com/privacy \n
3. Security \n
I am striving to use commercially acceptable means of protecting your Personal
Information. But remember that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of
electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable, and I cannot guarantee its absolute
security. \n
4. Links to Other Sites \n
This Service may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link, you
will be directed to that site. Note that these external sites are not operated by me.
Therefore, I strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these websites. I have
no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or
practices of any third-party sites or services. \n
5. Children’s Privacy \n
These Services do not address anyone under the age of 16. I do not knowingly collect
personally identifiable information from children under 16. In the case I discover that
a child under 16 has provided me with personal information, I immediately delete those
informations. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has
provided personal information, please contact me so that I will be able to do necessary
actions. \n
6. Distribution \n
The only official channel for distribution of this app are:
* Google Play Store https://play.google.com/
* XDA Developers Android Forum https://www.xda-developers.com/
Any other mode of distribution is not official and thus, is not maintained by the developer.
This privacy policy is effective to distribution made on official channel only. \n


7.Google analitycs \n
Our applications use Google Analytics. Google Analytics is a web analytics tool that helps website owners understand how visitors interact with their website. Google Analytics customers can view a variety of reports on how visitors interact with their website so that they can improve it. Google Analytics collects information anonymously. Reports website trends without identifying individual visitors. \n
10. Changes to This Privacy Policy \n
This policy may be updated from time to time. \n
Contact me \n
If you have any questions or suggestions about my Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to
contact me"</string>

</resources>